<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AI Motorsport Family</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AI Motorsport Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:50:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Practice Prawn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/practiceprawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/practiceprawn/</guid>
      <description>Practice Prawn, a name synonymous with excellence and victory in the fast-paced world of motorsports. Established with a vision for success and a commitment to pushing the boundaries of racing, Practice Prawn has emerged as a powerhouse in the GT3.Life Championship, etching their name in the annals of motorsport history.&#xA;In 2023, Practice Prawn soared to new heights, clinching the GT3.Life Constructors&amp;rsquo; Championship with their mastery of the track and unwavering determination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prawn GP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prawngp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prawngp/</guid>
      <description>Prawn GP, a team that dances to the beat of their own drum in the thrilling world of motorsports. With a whimsical spirit and a unique approach to racing, Prawn GP brings a refreshing blend of fun and flair to the track, capturing the hearts of fans worldwide.&#xA;Behind the wheel of Prawn GP&amp;rsquo;s vibrant racing machines are the dynamic duo of drivers, Matt Lawn and Russell Swain-Fossey. While championship glory may not be their primary aim, Lawn and Swain-Fossey infuse every race with their infectious energy and unwavering enthusiasm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuedria Practice Prawn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scuedriapracticeprawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scuedriapracticeprawn/</guid>
      <description>Scuderia Practice Prawn, a name that evokes both precision and a dash of whimsy, embodies the spirit of relentless pursuit and unwavering dedication in the high-octane world of motorsports. Founded with a passion for racing excellence, the team has become a formidable presence in the 3GTUK Championship, setting hearts racing and adrenaline soaring with each turn of the wheel.&#xA;At the helm of Scuderia Practice Prawn&amp;rsquo;s roaring Ferrari 296 GT3 car, the team&amp;rsquo;s dynamic duo of drivers, Matthew Riley and Suhas Umashankar, stand as exemplars of skill and determination.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
